Weber Shandwick 2809 Boston St #8, Baltimore, MD 21224 May 11, 2017

Dear Dan,

I am writing to express interest in a web developer role at Weber Shandwick.

During my 16 years experience as a Web Designer and Front End Developer at R2integrated, DuClaw Brewing Company, North Charles Street Design Organization and the University of Maryland Baltimore County, I have honed my skills in web development using CSS/SASS, HTML, and JQuery. I have collaborated with art directors to deliver fully-functioning web sites within strict deadlines.

I am excited for the opportunity to bring my skills to one of the top public relations agencies in the world. Weber Shandwick offers a team-oriented environment, with plenty of room for growth and leadership potential, which also appeals to me.

Please visit <u>www.aaronweidele.com</u> to see examples of my work. If I may answer any additional questions for you, please do not hesitate to contact me at 443.207.1468 or at aweidele@gmail.com. Thank you for your time and consideration, and I look forward to speaking with you soon.

Sincerely,

Aaron Weidele

## **SKILLS**

Responsive web design

HTML, CSS/SASS/LESS

PHP

Javascript/JQuery

Wordpress

Sitecore

Git

SourceTree

Jira

Shopify

MySQL

Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Premiere, After Effects, Flash)

Web prototyping tools (Axure, Balsamic, HotGloo)

**UX** Design

**Usability Testing** 

Motion Graphics

Experience with Google Analytics

# **EDUCATION**

1995—2000

University of Maryland Baltimore County / B.A. Imaging and Digital Arts

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## 2016-Present Front-End Developer, R2integrated

Collaborated with designers, back-end developers, and QA to build websites and components in Sitecore

Built framework for future Sitecore projects to facilitate faster development

## 2014–2016 Front-End Developer, DuClaw Brewing Company

Worked with designers to develop microsites for festivals and special beer releases

Developed distributor order forms using PHP and MySQL

Migrated web store to Shopify, and set up Shopify POS for merchandise sales at festivals

# 2010–2014 Interactive Designer, North Charles Street Design Organization

Design and development of interactive recruitment campaigns for higher education. Campaigns included an email series and landing site.

Build custom Wordpress themes for advancement campaign websites.

Motion graphics for digital signs

#### Awards:

**Gold Award /** New Media / Higher Education Marketing Report's 27th Annual Educational Advertising Awards

**Silver Award /** Website / Higher Education Marketing Report's 26th Annual Educational Advertising Awards

**Silver Award /** Video Viewbook / Higher Education Marketing Report's 26th Annual Educational Advertising Awards

## 1999–2010 New Media Specialist, University of Maryland Baltimore County

Designed websites for university departments

Developed online Undergraduate Catalog

Developed online interactive campus map

Trained faculty and staff in content management

#### **Presentations:**

New Media Consortium / 2009 / Monterey, CA /

Poster presentation, "Finding Your Career Path," about the Career Path web site

**New Media Consortium /** 2005 / Honolulu, HI / 5 Minutes of Fame, "Building a Campus Map," a 5-minute presentation on building the interactive campus map of UMBC